<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ColchesterGuide</string>
    <string name="castle_park">Colchester Castle Park</string>
    <string name="zoo">Colchester zoo</string>
    <string name="park">Wivenhoe Trail</string>
    <string name="art">Firstsite</string>
    <string name="ruins">St Botolph\'s Priory</string>
    <string name="park2">Highwoods Country Park</string>
    <string name="res1">El Guaca Mexican Grill</string>
    <string name="res2">Nandos</string>
    <string name="res3">Pitta Lab</string>
    <string name="res4">Purple Dog</string>
    <string name="res5">Kaspa\'s Desserts</string>
    <string name="res6">Church Street Tavern</string>
    <string name="res1_info">Vibrant, low-key eatery serving Mexican cuisine such as taco plates plus beers &amp; margaritas.</string>
    <string name="res2_info">Afro-Portuguese chain restaurant serving flame-grilled chicken in spicy chilli sauce.</string>
    <string name="res3_info">Greek restaurant on the wheels serving amazing pitta wraps.</string>
    <string name="res4_info">Enduring tavern for eclectic pub fare, ales &amp;amp coffee, including Sunday roasts, plus a beer garden. Nice place to relax and grab a drink.</string>
    <string name="res5_info">A great place to treat yourself with waffles, gelatos and many more desserts.</string>
    <string name="res6_info">Old school pub with retro set up. Well if you are a fan of live music then this where you should be, sipping that whiskey, munching crisps and enjoying live music.</string>
    <string name="castle_info">Colchester Castle Park is situated to the north east of Colchester Town Centre and is divided into the Upper Park and Lower Park by the Roman Wall that crosses through it east to west. The park spans an area of 11 hectares and is listed Grade II in the English Register of Parks and Gardens of Special Historic Importance.
        The Castle Museum, Hollytrees Museum, Play Park, Cafe, Crazy Golf and Bandstand are located in the Upper Park next to the Town Centre. Both are Grade II listed buildings and the Upper Park lies inside the Conservation Area of the Town Centre. The Lower Park is adjacent to the cricket ground and expands downwards to the River Colne.So whether you want to visit the museums and gardens or just relax and enjoy your free time by sitting, walking, enjoying music, picnicking or playing games in an expansive oasis of green and nature, Colchester Castle Park is the place to be.</string>
    <string name="zoo_info">Colchester Zoo is a zoological garden situated near Colchester, England. The zoo opened in 1963 and celebrated its 50th anniversary on 2 June 2013. This Zoo is home to 220 species set in 60 acres of parkland and lakes! As you navigate your way around Colchester Zoo you’ll visit many different habitats and see animals from around the world, from the humid home of our Komodo Dragons to our very own Africa plain,  home to white rhino, giraffes, ostrich, zebra and kudu!</string>
    <string name="park_info">One of the most popular walks in Colchester, the Wivenhoe Trail is an informal route of about 5 miles, stretching from Colchester town centre to the riverside town of Wivenhoe. Pick the trail up in Castle Park by the riverside and simply follow the River Colne as it flows out to sea. Download our Town to Sea leaflet for a more detailed map of the first half of the walk and stops of interest. As the Town to Sea trail finishes the path beside the river on it\'s north bank will be clear and can be followed all the way to Wivenhoe. If you are a smart phone user we recommend using the Go Jauntly app which covers the entire trail.</string>
    <string name="art_info">Firstsite is a visual arts organisation based in Colchester, Essex, which opened in 2011. The building Firstsite occupy as tenants was designed by Rafael Viñoly and the freehold is retained by Colchester Council.The gallery\'s opening received a considerable evaluation in the press. </string>
    <string name="ruins_info">Founded about 1100, St Botolph\'s was one of the first Augustinian priories in England. An impressive example of early Norman architecture, built in flint and reused Roman brick, the church displays massive circular pillars, round arches and an elaborate west front. It was badly damaged by cannon fire during the Civil War siege of 1648. Read more about the history of the priory. Colchester is also home to the remains of another medieval religious house at St John\'s Abbey Gate, just a few minutes walk away from St Botolph\'s Priory. Also in Colchester are the Iron Age defences of pre-Roman Colchester at Lexden Earthworks and Bluebottle Grove. </string>
    <string name="park2_info">Meadow &amp; forest country park with a lake, play areas, Nordic walking trail &amp; a community garden. High Woods Country Park is one of Colchester\'s beauty spots. The park provides habitats for thousands of different birds and mammals, including woodland, a lake, wildflower meadows, marshes, hayfields, scrubland, and open spaces (ideal for picnics). </string>
    <string name="history">Colchester is a historic town located in Essex, England. It served as the first capital of Roman Britain and is oldest recorded town in Britain.</string>
    <string name="history_body">Whilst Colchester is perhaps best known as a Roman city its history stretches back well beyond that with an ancient Iron Age settlement, once ruled by Cuneobelin \'King of the Britons\' established here long before the Romans arrived. Beyond a few earthen mounds little from this period has survived in the landscape, but numerous artifacts have been discovered over the years and an impressive collection is on display in the Castle Museum. Following the Roman Invasion in AD43 a city was established on the site of Camulodunum and designated the Roman capital of Britannia. It\'s destruction at the hands of Boudicca is well documented, but the Roman settlement rose up again and the remains of several buildings from this period can still be seen on a trip to the town. For more info click on the link below.</string>
    <string name="shopping_title">The Lion Walk</string>
    <string name="shopping">The Lion Walk is the shopping hub located on the High Street of Colchester. It is surrounded with different shops including barbers, restaurants, pubs, big brands like Top Man, Marks &amp; Spencers /n There is also this Colchester market that sets up every week ranging from fresh fruits, vegetables, fish, to deli food.</string>
    <string name="colchester">Colchester is a historic market town and the largest settlement within the borough of Colchester in the county of Essex. Colchester occupies the site of what was Camulodunum, the first major Roman city in, and sometime capital of, Roman Britain. Colchester lays claim to be Britain\'s oldest recorded town. Colchester has been a military garrison since the Roman era and is currently home to the 16th Air Assault Brigade. Situated on the River Colne, Colchester is 50 miles (80 kilometres) northeast of London and is connected to the capital by the A12 road and its railway station which is on the Great Eastern Main Line. It is seen as a popular town for commuters, and is less than 30 miles (50 km) from London Stansted Airport and 20 miles (30 km) from the passenger ferry port of Harwich. Colchester is home to Colchester Castle and Colchester United Football Club. There are several theories about the origin of the name Colchester. Some contend that is derived from the Latin words colonia (referring to a type of Roman settlement with rights equivalent to those of Roman citizens, one of which was believed to have been founded in the vicinity of Colchester) and castra, meaning fortifications (referring to the town\'s walls, the oldest in Britain). The earliest forms of the name Colchester are Colenceaster and Colneceastre from the 10th century, with the modern spelling of Colchester being found in the 15th century. In this way of interpreting the name, the River Colne which runs through the town takes its name from Colonia as well.</string>
    <string name="colchester_line"> The town is filled with classic and old school pubs and taverns. The Colchester market is one of the biggest market that is setup weekly. Ranging from fresh fruits, vegetables and meat products sold at reasonably fair price. The HighStreet is filled eateries and shops and showrooms, providing wide range of shopping option to the visitors.</string>
    <string name="bus_services">Bus Services</string>
</resources>